http://www.girlscoutsnca.org/en/our-council/privacy-policy.html

SIGN IN
OUR COUNCILAboutContact UsJoin UsCOVID-19 InformationForms and DocumentsFAQDigital Suggestion BoxShopAnnual Meeting InformationNewslettersBrand CenterCouncil Financial RecordsInternet Safety PledgeACTIVITIES VOLUNTEERS CAMPS COOKIES+SUPPORT USABOUT GIRL SCOUTSSIGN IN
Join
Forms
Shop
Donate
Español
Facebook
Contact
AboutContact UsJoin UsCOVID-19 InformationForms and DocumentsFAQDigital Suggestion BoxShopAnnual Meeting InformationNewslettersBrand CenterCouncil Financial RecordsInternet Safety Pledge
Our CouncilPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This Web site is owned by Girl Scouts of North-Central Alabama , a
501(c)(3) non-profit organization headquartered in Birmingham, AL.
[Our online properties comprise of, but are not limited to, all pages
found under girlscoutsnca.org & gsnca.org. This privacy policy
applies to these sites and other sites, mobile apps or other online
services we operate that link to this policy (collectively, referred
to below as the site).]
Girl Scouts of North-Central Alabama is committed to respecting and
protecting the privacy of our visitors. This privacy policy discloses
how we collect, protect, and use information you provide or we collect
online, as well as how we protect children's privacy. If our policy
practices change in the future, we will let you know by posting our
revised privacy policy on our Web site. By using the pages on this
site or other services covered by the posted Privacy Policy, you are
accepting the practices described in the Privacy Policy.
INFORMATION COLLECTION
Personally Identifiable Information. At our site, we do not collect
personally identifiable information from individuals unless they
provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means we do not
require you to register or provide information to us in order to view
our site. Girl Scouts of North-Central Alabama only gathers personally
identifiable data on our site, such as names, addresses, Zip/postal
codes, e-mail addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by a
visitor.  Once collected, we may combine this information with other
information collected from external sources.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information.  Girl Scouts of
North-Central Alabama may automatically collect certain technical
information from your computer such as your Internet service provider,
your Internet Protocol address, your browser type, your operating
system, the pages viewed, the pages viewed immediately before and
after accessing the Web site, and the search terms entered to get to
our site. This information allows us to improve and customize our
services. We and our service providers may collect this information
using “cookies,” which are small text files that many websites save on
your computer, or similar technologies. See the section on “Use of
Cookies and Similar Technology” below for more information.
USE AND SHARING OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
The personally identifiable information you provide is used by Girl
Scouts of North-Central Alabama and other entities who are involved in
the operation of this site or who provide support for the Girl Scouts
of North-Central Alabama and Girl Scouts of the USA mission and
programs, for general business purposes and for the purposes for which
you provided the information.  General business purposes include, for
example, Girl Scouts of North-Central Alabama and Girl Scouts of the
USA membership activities, program participation, marketing,
promotions, and fundraising activities and communications.  The
purposes for which you provide information includes our use of your
personally identifiable information to process online transactions,
purchases, and donations, facilitate participation in Girl Scouts of
the USA and Girl Scouts of North-Central Alabama programs, promotions
and services, or process job applications.  We do not sell information
you provide to us online with third parties.  We may share personally
identifiable information with third parties including: (i) with other
Girl Scout Councils and Girl Scout troops for administrative purposes
relating to a child’s activities with another Council or their troop;
(ii) when the person submitting the information authorizes us to share
it; (iii) when sharing the information is with a service provider in
furtherance of our operations or the operation of the site, for
instance, to process a purchase or other transaction you make; (iv) to
facilitate participation in Girl Scouts of the USA and Girl Scouts of
North-Central Alabama programs, promotions, and services, or to engage
in fund raising, marketing communications and promotions; (v) to
comply with legal processes such as a subpoena or court order or to
otherwise protect your or our legal rights; or (vi) for other purposes
for which you provided the information. Girl Scouts of North-Central
Alabama has no control over or responsibility for the data collection
and use practices of third parties that process online transactions.
For example, if you make a purchase on our site using a PayPal account
or similar account of a third party payment provider, certain
information is transmitted to the payment provider and is subject to
the third party’s own privacy policy.
Please note that Girl Scouts of the USA provides operational support
for the site and may collect and use personally identifiable
information you provide to the site and other information collected by
the site as described in this policy.  Girl Scouts of the USA will use
any information it collects for the purposes described in this policy
and in a manner consistent with its own privacy policy, which is
available here.  Girl
Scouts of North-Central Alabama and Girl Scouts of the USA are each
responsible for their own information handling practices.
CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
Girl Scouts of North-Central Alabama is committed to providing a
safe, secure, and fun online experience for children who visit our
site. We are dedicated to safeguarding any personally identifiable
information collected online and to helping parents and children have
positive experiences on the Internet.
We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information
from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental
consent. With parental consent, we may collect information from
children under the age of 13 such as: name, address, email address,
account information, and user generated content. This information
allows us to fulfill a requested transaction and facilitate
participation in online programs, keep records, undertake certain
marketing activities, or to otherwise customize or enhance the Web
site experience for children.
Children under the age of 13 may be able to make certain content
such as user generated content visible to others or the public. This
could include, for example, a webpage or parts of webpages operated by
children that have been designed for group or public viewing. However,
absent parental consent, children under 13 would be allowed to display
only limited information such as a first name or unique user name or
other information that does not allow for online contacting by third parties.
Regardless of what information is displayed, parents can revoke
their consent and ask that information about their children be deleted
from the site by contacting our offices by phone at 205-453-9540 or
via email. To do this
or to review personally identifiable information collected from
children, we must verify the identity of the requesting parent. When a
parent revokes consent, we will stop collecting, using, or disclosing
information from that child. To respect the privacy of parents,
information collected and used for the sole purpose of obtaining
verifiable parental consent or providing notice is not maintained in
retrievable form by the site if parental consent is not obtained after
a reasonable time.
Submissions
Girl Scouts of North-Central Alabama welcomes children to learn more
about our organization and, where appropriate, participate in polls
and surveys, as well as submit comments, artwork, writings, and other
submissions for posting on our Web site. For this reason, Girl Scouts
of North-Central Alabama follows the guidelines for interactive
electronic media published by the Children's Advertising Review Unit
(CARU) of the Better Business Bureau for pages targeted to children
under 13. However, we encourage this be done only with their parent's
knowledge and supervision. We also encourage children to use an alias
(e.g., "Bookworm", "Skater", etc.), first name,
nickname, initials, or other alternative to full names or screen names
which correspond with an e-mail address for any activities which will
involve public posting.
In keeping with CARU's Principle regarding respecting and fostering
the parents' role in providing guidance for their children, we
encourage parents to check and monitor their children's use of e-mail
and other online activities regularly.
USE OF COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES
Visitors should be aware that non-personal information and data may
be automatically collected by the Girl Scouts of North-Central Alabama
Web site through the use of "cookies" or other similar
technologies such as web beacons. "Cookies" are small text
files a Web site can use to recognize repeat visitors, facilitate the
visitor's ongoing access to and use of the site, and allow a site to
track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow
content improvements. Cookies are not programs that come onto a
visitor's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by
assigning a unique number to the visitor that has no meaning outside
the assigning site. If a visitor does not want information collected
through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most
browsers that allows the visitor to deny or accept the cookie feature.
“Web beacons” are a small snippet of code embedded in webpages
typically used to monitor activity on a webpage and transfer or
collect information, such as information about your Internet Protocol
address, the URL of the page on which the beacon is located, the
browser type that is accessing the site, and the ID number of cookies
placed on your computer.
Girl Scouts of North-Central Alabama uses "cookie"
technology only to obtain non-personal information from its online
visitors in order to improve visitors' online experience and
facilitate their visit within our site. Girl Scouts of North-Central
Alabama may use web beacons to improve website services, conduct
website analytics, first party advertising relating to us and our
sponsors, and to optimize the browsing experience.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit
our Web site. These companies may use non-personally
identifiable information (that is, not including your name, address,
e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and
other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and
services of interest to you on this or other websites. Read more
information about this
practice at http://www.networkadvertising.org
and http://www.aboutads.info/choices/
to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.
LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES AND SERVICES
This site may be linked to other sites and services that are not
maintained by Girl Scouts of North-Central Alabama . These Web sites
have their own privacy policies, which you should review prior to
visiting them. We have no responsibility for linked Web sites and
provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.
OUR SECURITY SAFEGUARD
The safety and security of your online experience is of the utmost
concern to us. We take measures to implement reasonable physical,
electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent
unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the
information we collect online.
Credit Card Safety
Protecting the safety of your credit card information is also
important to us.  For card transactions we process, we use Secure
Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your credit
card information as it is transmitted to us. SSL is an Internet
encryption technology, and a method of scrambling data as it travels
from your computer to our Web site servers. We also encrypt your
credit card number when we store your order and whenever we transfer
that information to participating merchants.
To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit
sensitive information, check the document for your browser for
indication of an SSL connection (most browsers utilize an unbroken or
closed padlock). Verify that SSL is active before submitting sensitive
information to our server. To double-check, verify that the URL or
Address line of your browser for our site begins with "https."
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to
your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished
using a shared computer.
Children
If you are under 18, you need parent/guardian permission to use a
credit card to make purchases online.
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact
us at:
will get back to you as soon as possible.
Thank you for visiting our site.
This Privacy Policy was last updated in October 2016
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
800-734-4541
